(Amy:)riding on a train for children
around the mall.
(Penny:)The little choo-choo
for toddlers?
(Amy:)And now you know why
I needed the massage.
(Howard:)Well, we're out.
(Howard:)Bernie can't drink
'cause she's pregnant.
(Howard:)And she's pregnant
because we had sex.
(Howard:)And we had sex because...
(laughs):
well, come on.
(Bernadette:)It's okay.
You should go.
(Howard:)You sure?
(Bernadette:)Of course.
(Penny:)Yeah, give her a break from,
“Well, come on.”
(Sheldon:)Well, Bernadette, looks like
Saturday night, it's you and me.
(Bernadette:)Me? How? Why?
(Sheldon:)Well, it makes perfect sense.
(Sheldon:)Because you're an expectant
mother, you can't drink alcohol.
(Sheldon:)I don't like to.
(Sheldon:)You can't have sushi.
(Sheldon:)You can't go in hot tubs.
(Sheldon:)I consider them
vats of sweaty people soup.
(Bernadette:)Gee, Sheldon, I don't know.
(Sheldon:)Oh, come on.
(Sheldon:)Roller coasters, caffeine,
runny eggs...
(Sheldon:)I've been avoiding these things
all my life.
(Sheldon:)And now, because you're
pregnant, you have to.
(Leonard:)The difference is she's
bringing life into the world,
(Leonard:)and you suck it out.
(Bernadette:)I guess we could give it a try.
(Sheldon:)Well, little lady,
you've heard of party hearty;
(Sheldon:)get ready to party hardly.
(Howard:)I bet you'd like
a drink right now.
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪